{
    "ar": {
        "code": "ar",
        "emoji": "🇸🇦",
        "name": "Arabic",
        "native": "العربية",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "تعديل الإجابة",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "السؤال رقم",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "cn": {
        "code": "cn",
        "emoji": "🇨🇳",
        "name": "Chinese",
        "native": "中文",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "正确",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "问题",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "nl": {
        "code": "nl",
        "emoji": "🇳🇱",
        "name": "Dutch",
        "native": "Nederlands",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Corrigeer",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Vraag",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "en": {
        "code": "en",
        "emoji": "🇬🇧",
        "name": "English",
        "native": "English",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Correct",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Question",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "fr": {
        "code": "fr",
        "emoji": "🇫🇷",
        "name": "French",
        "native": "Français",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Corriger",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Question",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "de": {
        "code": "de",
        "emoji": "🇩🇪",
        "name": "German",
        "native": "Deutsch",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Verbessern",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Frage",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "il": {
        "code": "il",
        "emoji": "🇮🇱",
        "name": "Hebrew",
        "native": "עברית",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "תיקון",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "שאלה",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "it": {
        "code": "it",
        "emoji": "🇮🇹",
        "name": "Italian",
        "native": "Italiano",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Correggi",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Domanda",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "jp": {
        "code": "jp",
        "emoji": "🇯🇵",
        "name": "Japanese",
        "native": "日本",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "修正する",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "質問",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "kr": {
        "code": "kr",
        "emoji": "🇰🇷",
        "name": "Korean",
        "native": "한국어",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "이전 질문",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "질문",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "pl": {
        "code": "pl",
        "emoji": "🇵🇱",
        "name": "Polish",
        "native": "Polski",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Popraw",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Pytanie",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "pt": {
        "code": "pt",
        "emoji": "🇵🇹",
        "name": "Portuguese",
        "native": "Português",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Corrigir",
            "cancel": "Cancelar",
            "yes": "Sim",
            "no": "Não",
            "question": "Pergunta",
            "guess": {
                "question": "Eu acho que",
                "ranked": "Classificado",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Excelente! Acertei mais uma vez!",
                    "description": "Adorei jogar com você!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "Você me venceu!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "ru": {
        "code": "ru",
        "emoji": "🇷🇺",
        "name": "Russian",
        "native": "Русский",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Исправить",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Вопрос",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "es": {
        "code": "es",
        "emoji": "🇪🇸",
        "name": "Spanish",
        "native": "Español",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Corregir",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Pregunta",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    },
    "tr": {
        "code": "tr",
        "emoji": "🇹🇷",
        "name": "Turkish",
        "native": "Türk",
        "texts": {
            "correct": "Düzelt",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "no": "No",
            "question": "Soru",
            "guess": {
                "question": "I think of",
                "ranked": "Ranked",
                "right": {
                    "title": "Great! Guessed right one more time.",
                    "description": "I love playing with you!"
                },
                "wrong": {
                    "title": "Bravo!",
                    "description": "You have defeated me!"
                }
            }
        }
    }
}